export default data = [
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/i:/' ?",
    options: ["idiot", "mean", "lip", "breakfast"],
    correct_option: "mean",
  },
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/ə/' ?",
    options: ["enter", "easy", "locked", "adding"],
    correct_option: "enter",
  },
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/ʃ/' ?",
    options: ["church", "think", "wish", "vision"],
    correct_option: "wish",
  },
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/æ/' ?",
    options: ["aardvark", "hare", "weight", "apple"],
    correct_option: "apple",
  },
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/eɪ/' ?",
    options: ["wait", "either", "ample", "sapling"],
    correct_option: "wait",
  },
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/^/' ?",
    options: ["shoe", "should", "moon", "puppy"],
    correct_option: "puppy",
  },
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/ʒ/' ?",
    options: ["shout", "wish", "change", "leisure"],
    correct_option: "leisure",
  },
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/əʊ/' ?",
    options: ["row (argument)", "sow (pig)", "now", "row (a boat)"],
    correct_option: "row (a boat)",
  },
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/ɔɪ/' ?",
    options: ["ought", "should", "house", "annoy"],
    correct_option: "annoy",
  },
  {
    question: "Please select a word that contains the sound '/ʊ/'",
    options: ["wood", "mood", "mop", "using"],
    correct_option: "wood",
  },
];
